Guide to the Brooklyn location scouting photographs collection CBHM.0017
Center for Brooklyn History
- Series 6: Borough Park, circa 1990 - circa 2007
  Series 6: Borough Park includes photographs of apartments, houses, bowling alleys, social clubs, streets and a construction site in the Borough Park neighborhood of Brooklyn from circa 1990 to circa 2007.
  - EXT Goldie's Apartment Building: New Utrecht Avenue, Borough Park, circa 1990 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    This folder was categorized under "Brooklyn Apartments." Includes photographs of 4401 New Utrecht Avenue, 4419 New Utrecht Avenue, and 4409 New Utrecht Avenue.
  - Maple Lanes, 1570 60th Street at 16th Avenue, circa 1990 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - EXT Construction site, 60th Street and 11th Avenue, circa 1990 (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - EXT Neighborhood, New Utrecht Avenue (between 65th Street and 56th Street, Borough Park and Bensonhurst, B Train, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Social Club, Louvin Co., 4000 10th Avenue at 40th Street, Borough Park, circa 1995 (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - EXT Neighborhood, Borough Park, New Utrecht Avenue, Fort Hamilton Parkway and 49th Street, B and M Fort Hamilton Stop, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - EXT Neigborhood, Borough Park, New Utrecht Avenue (at 12th Avenue and 49th Street), B and M trains, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - EXT/INT House, 949 41st Street (between 9th Avenue and New Utrecht Avenue), 1997 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - P.S. 164, 4211 14th Avenue at 42nd Street, 2002 (Box 78, Folder 1)
    This location was initially scouted for Doubt and reconsidered for Extremely Loud and Incredibly Close.
  - EXT/INT Bowling, Maple Lanes, 1570 60th Street at 16th Avenue, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - 1545 49th Street (between 15th Avenue and 16th Avenue), 2004 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - P.S. 164, EXT school, 4211 14th Avenue (between 42nd Street and 43rd Street), 2007 (Box 78, Folder 3)
    This location was scouted for Doubt and later considered for Extremely Loud and Incredibly Close.
  - P.S. 164, 14th Avenue between 42nd Street and 43rd Street, circa 2007 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Series 7: Brighton Beach, circa 1990 - 2011
  Series 7: Brighton Beach includes photographs of apartments, restaurants, and streets in the Brighton Beach neighborhood of Brooklyn from the 1990s to 2011.
  - EXT Joe and Pearl walk and talk, West 16th Street and Neptune Avenue, Brighton Beach, circa 1990 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    This location was scouted for Used People.
  - EXT Joe and Pearl walk and talk, Brighton Beach, circa 1990 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - EXT Pearl's, 3115 Brighton 4th Street and 3111 Brighton 7th Street, Brighton Beach, circa 1990 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - EXT Joe and Pearl Walk and Talk: Brighton 1st Place and Bright Water Court, circa 1990 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - EXT Joe and Pearl Walk and Talk, Brighton 15th Street and Corbin Place, Brighton Beach, circa 1990 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - EXT Neighborhood, Brighton 14th Street and Oceanside Avenue, Brighton Beach, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - EXT Club La Habanita, Oceana Theater, 1031 Brighton Beach Avenue to 1033 Brighton Beach Avenue, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - EXT Pearl's Apartment: 3111 Brighton 7th Street, Brighton Beach, circa 1995 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - 3111 Brighton 7th Street, Brighton Beach, circa 1995 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - INT Nightclub, Odessa, 1113 Brighton Beach Avenue (between Brighton 13th Street and Brighton 14th Street), circa 1995 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - EXT Neighborhood: Brighton Beach, Various Streets, D and Q Trains, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    This folder includes photographs of Brighton 3rd Street, Brighton 10th Street, Brighton 5th Street, Brighton 4th Street, Odessa, Taste of Russia, Café St. Petersburg, Black Sea Bookstore, and Brighton Beach Avenue.
  - INT Mehanata, Tatiana Restaurant, 3152 Brighton 6th Street, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - INT Mehanata Restaurant, Winter Garden, 3152 Brighton 6th Street, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - INT Mehanata Restaurant, The National, 273 Brighton Beach Avenue, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - EXT Black World, Brighton Beach Avenue, between Coney Island Avenue and Brighton Beach 12th Street, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - EXT Black World - under elevated, Brighton Beach Avenue at Brighton 6th Street, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - EXT Black World, Brighton Beach - elevated track views, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - EXT Black World, Brighton Beach, Brighton 7th Street and Brighton 8th Street, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Various - Ocean Parkway and Neptune Avenue, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - EXT Black World, Brighton 4th Street between Brighton Beach Avenue and Brightwater Court, 2010 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - INT/EXT Pre-war building - Various Blacks, 3115 Brighton [6th Street], 2011 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - INT/EXT Pre-war building - Various Blacks, 3099 [Brighton 6th Street], 2011 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - INT/EXT Coney Island House - Various Blacks, Brighton 7th Street at Brighton 8th Street, 2011 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Series 8: Brooklyn Heights, circa 1990 - circa 2010
  Series 8: Brooklyn Heights includes photographs of apartments, houses, parks, restaurants, bars, offices, schools, synagogues, and churches.
  - INT Bar, Clark Street Station, 78 Clark Street at Henry Street, Brooklyn Heights, circa 1990 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Brooklyn Heights Promenade, view of Downtown Manhattan from Columbia Heights at Orange Street, Cranberry Street, and Pineapple Street, Brooklyn Heights, circa 1990 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Broadway Supply Co., 15 Cadman Plaza, circa 1990 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - 2 Pierrepont Street Apt. 7B, circa 1990 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Foffe's Restaurant: 155 Montague Street, circa 1990 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Whitman Towers, 75 Henry Street at Orange Street, Brooklyn Heights, circa 1990 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - INT/EXT Bar, Montero's Bar [Montero Bar and Grill], 73 Atlantic Avenue (between Columbia Place and Hicks Street), Brooklyn Heights, circa 1990 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - 111 Hicks Street, Apt. 16E, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - INT/EXT Pier Warehouse, Pier 3, Fulton Terminal, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - INT Rachel's apartment, 75 Livingston Street Apt. 14A, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - INT/EXT Laurel's apartment, 143 Willow Street, Brooklyn Heights, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    This location was scouted for The Associate.
  - INT/EXT Laurel's Apartment, 38 Grace Court, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - INT/EXT Laurel's apartment, 105 State Street (between Henry Street and Clinton Street), 1995 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - INT/EXT Laurel's apartment, 9 Pierrepont Street, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - INT/EXT Laurel's Apartment, 95 Joralemon Street, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - INT/EXT Laurel's apartment, 20 Garden Place, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - INT Laurel's, 295 Henry Street between State Street and Joralemon Street, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - INT Racquet Club, The Heights Casino, 75 Montague Street, 1995 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Scott and Cynthia's apartment, 202 Columbia Heights between Pierrepont Street and Clark Street, 1995 (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - Park Plaza Restaurant, 220 Cadman Plaza West at Pineapple Street, circa 1995 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - EXT Brooklyn Promenade, Pierrepont Street at Montague Terrace, circa 1995 (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - INT Bar, Park Slope Brewing Company, Brooklyn Heights location, 62 Henry Street, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - INT Bar Three Exits Café, Montague Street Saloon, 122 Montague Street, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - INT Bar, Annie's Blue Moon, 156 Montague Street, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - INT Mrs. Wiggins' apartment, 129 Columbia Heights Apt. 42, between Clark Street and Pierrepont Street, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 38)
    This folder was categorized under "Brooklyn Apartments."
  - 2 Grace Court, Brooklyn Heights, Apt. 1N, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Brooklyn Heights Promenade, 1996 (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - EXT/INT R and S Building, INT Rachel's apartment, 195 Hicks Street, Apt. 2A, 1996 (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - INT Loft/Apartment, 8 Hunts Lane, Brooklyn Heights, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - INT/EXT Tony's Townhouse, 48 Sidney Place (between Joralemon Street and State Street), Brooklyn Heights, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - INT Office [Express Research Services, 50 Court Street], 1997 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - EXT/INT R and S Building, INT Rachel's Apartment, 75 Pierrepont Street, Apt. 6E, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - EXT School: St. Charles Borromeo School, 23 Sidney Place, Brooklyn Heights, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    This folder was categorized under "Airports, Theaters, Gas Stations, Schools, Construction Sites, Hotels."
  - Blow Up: Everit Street (Columbia Heights) between Middagh Street and Old Fulton, circa 1998 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    This location was scouted for The Siege.
  - INT Synagogue, Kane Street Synagogue, 236 Kane Street between Court Street and Clinton Street, Brooklyn Heights, 1999 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Rooftop, 73 Columbia Street, 1999 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Warehouse/Pier, Pier 3, Port Authority of New York and New Jersey, circa 2000 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - EXT Warehouse, Piers 1-9 (south of Brooklyn Bridge), Port Authority, Brooklyn Heights, circa 2000 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - INT/EXT Brooklyn Heights Townhouse, 79 State Street, circa 2000 (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - 143 Willow Street, circa 2000 (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - INT/EXT Townhouse, 92 State Street (between Garden Place and Hicks Street), Brooklyn Heights, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - INT/EXT Townhouse, 96 State Street (between Garden Place and Henry Street), 2001 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Brooklyn Heights Promenade, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - EXT Townhouse, 88 Joralemon Street, Brooklyn Heights, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    This folder was categorized under "Brooklyn Neighborhoods." This location was scouted for Extremely Loud and Incredibly Close.
  - EXT Townhouse, 96 Remsen Street, Brooklyn Heights, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - INT/EXT Townhouse, 218 Columbia Heights, Brooklyn Heights, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - EXT Townhouse, 94 Joralemon Street, Brooklyn Heights, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - EXT Townhouse, Brooklyn Bar Association Office, 123 Remsen Street, Brooklyn Heights, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - INT/EXT Townhouse, 150 Columbia Heights at Clark Street, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - EXT Brownstone, 138 Columbia Heights, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - EXT Prior's, 194 Columbia Heights at Clark Street, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    This location was scouted for Angels in America.
  - EXT Townhouse, 34 Remsen Street (at Hicks Street), 2002 (Box 79, Folder 10)
  - INT/EXT Brooklyn Apartment, 178 Hicks Street (between Pierrepont Street and Clark Street), 2003 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Apartment Building Exteriors, Brooklyn Heights, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    This folder includes photographs of 62 Montague Street (between Montague Terrace and Hicks Street), 70 Remsen Street (between Hicks Street and Henry Street), 76 Remsen Street (between Hicks Street and Henry Street), 39 Remsen Street (between Montague Terrace and Hicks Street), 123 Remsen Street (Brooklyn Bar Association, between Henry Street and Clinton Street), 2 Montague Terrace (at Montague Street), 187 Hicks Street (between Pierrepont Street and Love Lane), 169 Colunbia Heights (between Clark Street and Montague Street), 129 Columbia Heights (between Clark Street and Pineapple Street).
  - EXT Parking lot, 7 Everit Street at Old Fulton Street, Brooklyn Heights, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Brooklyn Heights Synagogue, Remsen Street (between Clinton Street and Henry Street), 2003 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - INT Dr. Munce's office, 253 Henry Street at Joralemon Street, Brooklyn Heights, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    This location was scouted for The Forgotten.
  - EXT Police Precinct - Empty, 68 Poplar Street (between Hicks Street and Henry Street), 2003 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - INT/EXT Brooklyn Townhouse, 3 Pierrepont Place (at Montague Street), 2003 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    This folder was categorized under "Brownstones Brooklyn."
  - Brooklyn Heights Neighborhoods, 2003 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - INT/EXT Brooklyn Apartment, 103 State Street, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - EXT Grandma's House (NY for Boston), 16 Sidney Place at Aitken Place, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    This location was scouted for War of the Worlds.
  - EXT Townhouse, 24 Remsen Street at Montague Terrace, 2004 (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - EXT Townhouse, 56 Garden Place at State Street, Brooklyn Heights, 2004 (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - EXT Townhouse, 77 Columbia Heights at Cranberry Street, 2004 (Box 83, Folder 10)
  - Telly's Street: Joralemon Street between Willow Place and Columbia Street, circa 2004 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Brooklyn Promenade [Brooklyn Heights Promenade], circa 2005 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - EXT Pitt Apartment: 23 Pierrepont Street, Brooklyn Heights, circa 2005 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - EXT Grandma's House, 108 Pierrepont Street at Monroe Place, Brooklyn Heights, circa 2005 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - EXT Warren Townhouse, 218 Columbia Heights, circa 2005 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Townhouse, 259 Henry Street (between Remsen Street and Joralemon Street), circa 2005 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Roofline (only): 48 Pierrepont Street to 60 Pierrepont Street, circa 2005 (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - 18 College Place, circa 2005 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    This folder was categorzed under "Apartments/Lofts."
  - Cranberry Street between Columbia Heights and Willow Street, circa 2005 (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Willow Street between Pierrepont Street and Clark Street, circa 2005 (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Brooklyn Heights [Promenade], 2007 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Park Plaza Diner, 220 Cadman Plaza West at Clark Street, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - EXT Church, First Presbyterian Church of Brooklyn, 124 Henry Street (between Clark Street and Pierrepont Street), 2007 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - EXT Church, Zion German Evangelical Lutheran Church, Henry Street (between Clark Street and Pierrepont Street), 2007 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - EXT Church, First Presbyterian Church of Brooklyn, 124 Henry Street (between Clark Street and Pierrepont Street), 2007 (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - INT/EXT Abby Black, 176 Columbia Heights (between Clark Street and Pierrepont Street), Brooklyn Heights, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - INT/EXT Abby Black, 111 Columbia Heights, Brooklyn Heights, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Brooklyn Bridge Park, Furman Street between Old Fulton Street and Atlantic Avenue, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Rooftop: 195 Hicks at Pierrepont Street, circa 2010 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - 43 Pierrepont Street, northwest corner of Hicks Street/Pierrepont Street, circa 2010 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - 46 Old Fulton Street loft, 46 Cadman Plaza West, Brooklyn Heights, circa 2010 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Black World - Columbia Place at Joralemon Street (Brooklyn Heights), circa 2010 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Brooklyn Bridge Park, Furman Street, circa 2010 (Box 6, Folder 42)
- Series 9: Brooklyn Navy Yard, circa 1990 - 2010
  Series 9: Brooklyn Navy Yard includes photographs of piers and buildings of the Brooklyn Navy Yard from circa 1990 to 2010.
  - Cape Avinof at Brooklyn Navy Yard, Pier C, B and A Marine, circa 1990 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Stern of Cape Ann/Cape Avinof at Brooklyn Navy Yard, Pier C, B and A Marine, circa 1990 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Cape Ann, Brooklyn Navy Yard, Pier C, circa 1990 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - EXT Docks, Brooklyn Navy Yard, 1992 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Brooklyn Navy Yard, Scout by Boat, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - EXT Scrapyard, Brooklyn Navy Yard, Flushing Avenue at Cumberland Street, 1993 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Brooklyn Navy Yard, Building #3, Room 1108-1109, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Brooklyn Navy Yard, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    This folder also includes photographs of the 115th Street Firehouse at 81 West 115th Street.
  - Brooklyn Navy Yard, Building 30, 1994 (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - EXT Meeting Place, Brooklyn Navy Yard, circa 1995 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - INT Vacant Space, Brooklyn Navy Yard, Building 30, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - INT Prison Yard, Brooklyn Navy Yard, 1997 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Shop Space, Brooklyn Navy Yard, Building #5, 1997 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - EXT/INT Warehouse, Brooklyn Navy Yard off Flushing Avenue, 1997 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Holding area, Brooklyn Navy Yard, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    This folder was categorized under "Industrial Parks."
  - Back Lot Build Site, Former Navy Hospital, Brooklyn Navy Yard, 2004 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Brooklyn Navy Yard, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - GMD Shipyard, Brooklyn Navy Yard, Building 595, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - EXT East River docks, GMD Ship Repair, 63 Flushing Avenue at Clinton Street, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - EXT Final Battle, Steiner Studios, Brooklyn Navy Yard, 15 Washington Avenue gate, 2009 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - INT Barge, GMD Shipyard Corporation, Brooklyn Navy Yard, 2009 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - EXT Mansion, [Brooklyn Naval] Hospital, Brooklyn Navy Yard, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Series 10: Brownsville, 1993 - 2004
  Series 10: Brownsville includes photographs of publis housing and streets in the Brownsville neighborhood of Brooklyn from 1993 to 2004.
  - EXT Club La Habanita, Lot at 2190-2196 Fulton Street, between Eastern Parkway and Rockaway Avenue, 1993 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Housing Project, Van Dyke Housing, Dumont Avenue and Mother Gaston Boulevard, Brownsville, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - EXT Intersection, Pitkin Avenue at Saratoga Avenue, Brownsville, 2004 (Box 85, Folder 8)
  - Housing Project, Langston Hughes Houses, Sutter Avenue and Osborn Street, Brownsville, 2004 (Box 87, Folder 9)
- Series 11: Bushwick, circa 1990 - circa 2010
  Series 11: Bushwick includes photographs of schools, apartments, parks, stores, churches, and streets in the Bushwick neighborhood of Brooklyn from circa 1990 to circa 2010.
  - Ingraham Street between Porter Avenue and Knickerbocker Avenue [Bushwick], circa 1990 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - INT/EXT School, P.S. 120, Beaver Street, Bushwick, circa 1995 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Linden Street between Bushwick Avenue and Broadway, circa 1995 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - EXT Neighborhood, Bushwick, Myrtle Avenue and Broadway, M Train, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - EXT Neighborhood, Bushwick, Broadway and Thornton Street, Broadway and Fayette Street, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - INT Sheriff's Apartment, 48 Cornelia Street at Bushwick Avenue, 2nd Floor, Bushwick, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    This location was scouted for Return to Paradise and considered for Extremely Loud and Incredibly Close.
  - INT/EXT Hospital, Wyckoff Heights Medical Center, Bushwick, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - EXT Neighborhood, Bushwick, Heisser Square [Triangle], Myrtle Avenue and Bleecker Street, M Train, Knickerbocker Avenue Stop, 1997 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - EXT Neighborhood and car lot, Freedom Triangle - Bushwick, Myrtle Avenue and Bushwick Avenue ("M" train), 1997 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Spin Brudge, Grand Avenue [Grand Street Bridge], 1998 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - 12 Jefferson Street (Bushwick Avenue and Broadway), circa 2000 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Broadway and Myrtle Avenue, 2002 (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Maria Hernandez Park, Knickerbocker Avenue at Suydam Street, Bushwick, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Miscellaneous Street, Myrtle Avenue between Bushwick Avenue and Broadway, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Irving Square Park, Knickerbocker Avenue and Wilson Avenue, between Weirfield Street and Halsey Street, Bushwick, 2003 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - EXT Intersection, Bushwick Avenue and Jefferson Street, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - EXT Rooftop and INT dojo, Gembuken Dojo, Broadway at Myrtle Avenue, Bushwick, circa 2005 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    This folder was categorized under "Brooklyn Rooftops and Theaters."
  - EXT Street/Elevated rail area, Broadway at Vernon Avenue, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Streets with Elevated Trains, Broadway and Stewart Street, Conway Street, Eastern Parkway, and Cooke Court, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - EXT Street with Elevated Rail, Broadway at Myrtle Avenue, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Street with Elevated Trains, Myrtle Avenue at Stockholm Street, Stanhope Street, and Evergreen Avenue, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Streets with Elevated Trains, Myrtle Avenue at Himrod Street and Harmon Street, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - INT/EXT Loft, 88 Porter Avenue / 119 Ingraham Street, Bushwick, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - INT/EXT Loft, 505 Johnson Avenue, Bushwick, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Richie's Loft, 1087 Flushing Avenue at Knickerbocker Avenue, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Richie's Loft, 114 Forrest Street, Apt. 15 (between Flushing Avenue and Central Avenue), 2006 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - EXT Harlem Street, Broadway, Myrtle Avenue, and Melrose Street, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - EXT Myrtle Avenue and Broadway - Night, Harlem streets between Myrtle Avenue and Melrose Street, 2006 (Box 79, Folder 11)
  - INT/EXT Universal Bronze and Steel Door Company, 1171 Myrtle Avenue (at Troutman Street), 2006 (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - INT/EXT Store, Good Day 99 cents and Up, 957 Broadway (at Myrtle Avenue), 2006 (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - INT/EXT Store, Broadway Newsstand and Grocery, 932 Broadway (at Myrtle Avenue), 2006 (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - EXT/INT Social Club, 935 Broadway (at Myrtle Avenue), 2006 (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - Broadway at Lawton Street, Dodworth Street, and Dekalb Avenue, 2006 (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Broadway and Eldert Street, 2006 (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Streets, Myrtle Avenue and Central Avenue, Dekalb Avenue, Cedar Street, 2006 (Box 86, Folder 6)
  - Streets, Broadway and Greene Avenue, 2006 (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - EXT Houses, Maspeth Avenue and Conselyea Street, 2006 (Box 86, Folder 10)
  - St. Thomas Episcopal Church, 1405 Bushwick Avenue (between Moffat Street and Cooper Street), 2007 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - EXT/INT Schoool, St. Mark's Lutheran Church and School, 626 Bushwick Avenue (between Jefferson Street and Troutman Street), 2007 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - EXT School, P.S. 86 [The Irvington School], 220 Irving Avenue at Harman Street, 2007 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Bushwick Leadership School, Bushwick Avenue at Dekalb Avenue, 2007 (Box 81, Folder 9)
  - INT Barge, Themis Chimney, Inc., 190 Morgan Avenue at Stagg Street, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - EXT Josh Neighborhood, Dodworth Street (between Broadway and Bushwick Avenue), Bushwick, 2010 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - EXT Josh Neighborhood, Broadway at Lafayette Avenue, 2010 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - EXT Josh Neighborhood, Van Buren Street (between Broadway and Bushwick Avenue), Bushwick, 2010 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - EXT Josh Neighborhood, Evergreen Avenue at Menahan Street, Bushwick, 2010 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - EXT Josh Neighborhood, Irving Avenue (between Palmetto Street and Gates Avenue), Bushwick, 2010 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - EXT Josh Neighborhood, Palmetto Street at Ridgewood Place, Bushwick, 2010 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - EXT Neighborhood, Broadway and Myrtle Avenue, 2010 (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - EXT Josh's Neighborhood, Gates Avenue at Broadway, Bushwick, circa 2010 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - EXT Josh's Neighborhood, Central Avenue at Chauncey Street, Bushwick, circa 2010 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - EXT Josh's Neighborhood, Somers Street at Broadway, Bushwick, circa 2010 (Box 8, Folder 26)
- Series 12: Canarsie, 1987
  Series 12: Canarsie includes a photograph of the Abbracciamento restaurant building on the Canarsie pier in 1987.
  - Abbracciamento, Canarsie Pier, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    This location was scouted for Goodfellas.
- Series 13: Carroll Gardens, circa 1990 - circa 2011
  Series 13: Carroll Gardens includes photographs of restaurants, apartments, houses, and streets in the Caroll Gardens neighborhood of Brooklyn from circa 1990 to circa 2011.
  - Smith Street at 3rd Street, circa 1990 (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - Sam's Restaurant, 238 Court Street at Baltic Street, Carroll Gardens, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Red Rose Restaurant, 315 Smith Street at Union St, Carroll Gardens, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Vacant Store, 498 Smith Street at Garnet Street, Carroll Gardens, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Stanton's Townhouse, 237 Union Street, circa 1995 (Box 9, Folder 5)